We thought you were a veteran warrior.
But it seems..
...you are now going on
campaigns with raiders.
It doesn't suit you, Osman Bey.
Were you going to take Lefke like this?
If we are so worthless,
-Why did he send his son...
-We fight for Islam!
It doesn't matter with whom or what for.
We always intend to conquer!
I like this upright stand of yours.
You are a brave man.
But it doesn't suit you, Osman Bey.
-Come on!
-Lefke Castle..
..is your property now!
Settle in with your alps.
May your reputation spread among Turkmen!
May many brave warriors stand beside you!
What are you saying, Yakup Bey?
This place is your sword right.
You took it by fighting.
Why would it be my property? Why?
Because you are the one who fights most.
Lefke is our closest border to Byzantine.
It will be headquarters for conquests.
For this reason, Lefke..
...should belong to Osman Bey who has been
fighting from father to son.
Thank you.
Do you doubt the firman?
No. You took Lefke.
You conquered this place.
You left me nothing to doubt.
This is what you were expected to do, anyway.
We expect some things from you too, Osman Bey.
When will you pledge loyalty?
Yakup Bey.
When the Messenger of the Worlds
(PBUH) passed away,
...even Hadhrat Ali (RA)...
...didn't pledge loyalty for
Hadhrat Abu Bakr(RA) instantly.
Don't push me.
Besides, a quick oath of loyalty...
..would be no good.
You are right, but...
We should be united these days.
These are the last days of humanity.
You should be quick.
Cerkutay Bey has found the right way.
He's under my command.
He's the patron of the frontier market now.
What?
I guess you don't like this, Osman Bey.
Quite the contrary.
Well... Instead of walking around aimlessly,
he should be with Yakup Bey.
So he will do his duties properly.
Tomorrow, come to the frontier
market with your family.
We shall eat and talk about conquests.
And about loyalty.
This matter should come to a conclusion.
I will come to talk about conquests.
Your upright head will either
bow or leave your shoulders, Osman.
He doesn't intend to make me bow, but crush me.
Make whatever game you want. I will ruin your games.
Orhan, stop.
You're wounded so you need to rest.
This isn't a good time for resting, Holofira.
Crusaders must have hit the road
to take the gold to their lands.
I need to catch them and take the gold.
Otherwise I will never be able to take it.
But you're not coming. You will go to a safe place.
No.
-I can't leave you like this.
-Holofira.
I need to catch the crusaders. Let me go.
How do you know they are crusaders?
They were wearing crusader clothes, Dervish.
Is this your proof?
You only saw their clothes.
Do you know their hearts?
Let's say we made this tree wear clothes.
Would it become a human?
You say the attackers weren't crusaders?
I don't know that.
-Karaali.
-My Shahzade.
Now go and bring what I want.
Listen to me well.
-Come on.
-As you order, my Shahzade.
Thank you for healing me, Dervish.
Now I should get going.
Allah is the Healer.
-Stay safe.
-Thank you.
My Bey, why did Yakup Bey hand over Lefke?
He is showing power, brother.
He wants to seem generous
and strengthen his position.
Pardon my curiosity, my Bey.
But why did you accept it?
Yakup Bey has never been honest to us.
He's making such a game that
if you don't act cautiously...
...you can find yourself in chains.
He handed over the castle but he thought
I wouldn't take the castle.
If I hadn't taken it,
he would have convinced the beys.
He would have said "I gave him a castle.
He didn't even take it."
He doesn't want to fight for Islam.
He's arrogant and has a problem with me."
He would have said "Osman Bey is our enemy".
"He doesn't even mind firman or conquest."
Is the firman real, Osman Bey?
The seal is real.
But the firma
Sultan gave the treasure to us.
Why would he give him the firman?
There must be a trick about it.
Taking even Cerkutay on his side is a part of his game.
He does it to be able to say
"Even his own men come to me".
He attacks from all directions.
You're right, Bala.
He isn't like any enemies
who we have fought so far.
So we should be careful.
'ueuiso
Why did you let Cerkutay go?
If you had held him here,
he might have understood.
Bala, sometimes a sentence...
...says a thousand.
You know what he said to me?
"Osman Bey,
...I remained a prisoner
for years for your cause."
Now tell me. Tell me!
Is this Osman Bey's cause?
This is the cause of Allah.
This is the cause of our Prophet (PBUH).
We serve this cause. Don't we, Boran?
Konur? Tell me.
-This is the cause of Allah.
-There is no self.
We serve Him. That's why I let him go.
Well, there is nothing to do but praying
for him to come back to the path of Allah.
But there is something to do about Yakup Bey.
Quickly as well.
Konur.
You will keep order at the castle.
Do not leave the Bannerless alone.
As you command, Bey.
-Bora.
-Bey.
Look at each secret passage.
Count the warehouse after counting the spoils.
As you command.
Tell Alaeddin to not leave Yakup Bey alone.
-As you command, Bey.
-Quickly.
My Bala.
-Come on.
-I can not come to Yenisehir, Osman.
Bala, what are you saying?
You are better than before now.
-No, Osman.
-Bala.
Sogut is entrusted to me,
as the state is entrusted to you.
And my father is not here.
You are on a difficult path, Osman.
You need people beside you.
The guild, sisters..
I need to take care of them.
Here is where people grow.
My Bala, I understand you well.
After all the sacrifice you made..
Will lead us to victory
against the enemy, however..
Bala.
The tracks of carts and horses.
Is more visible here.
These are theirs.
Let us go after them at once.
Orhan. I know, your blood boils.
However, I don't want you to do something
unwise when you find them.
Those gold coins, is the future of my nation.
And my task is clear.
I will do everything I can to get that treasure.
Even if it costs your life?
Even if it costs my life.
Burn them in the cave.
We've got double the spoils in one raid..
Compared to pillaging,
all thanks to you Mehmet Bey.
Doing business with you is profitable.
Yes, Atmaca.
This is the power of Germiyanoglu.
Those who serve..
Fill their sacks with plenty of gold like this.
We will do more business with you
in the future, Mehmet Bey.
Those who wish to bring these
gold coins to the frontier bazaar..
And want to reach our power will fail.
My Shahzade. Caravan is ready to depart.
Quickly then, we will take
no breaks until frontier bazaar.
-Gonca Hatun.
-Hear what you're saying.
-Baysungur.
-My Shahzade.
Sheathe your swords and stay back.
Gulce.
-Were you scared?
-You know that I did not.
I have no business with
your father as well, Trickster Hatun.
I was very bored at the bazaar.
And since no one is racing horses.
Then I said,
"If I go out of this bazaar now.."
"Who would follow me?"
-Of course the Trickster Hatun.
-Allah Allah.
You did all this confusion for horse racing?
Don't you think it was worth it?
We could not do it last time.
Maybe this time I will beat you.
However, no trickery.
If I win, you will not call me trickster anymore.
Alright. What if I win?
You won't.
Let's say you did,
what do you want?
You can find out after Trickster Hatun.
Alright.
-To the bazaar then.
-Alright.
As you say, Trickster Hatun.
This was the last time
you called me Trickster Hatun.
We will see.
Quickly.
-Quickly!
Come on!
Quickly!
My Bey, public order was
maintained at castle.
The secret passages are being searched,
we are putting up guards.
Yakup Bey and his men
did not touch the treasure, Bey.
All of it is there.
Alright.
-Quickly.
-May your conquest be glorious, Osman Bey.
You are a providential man.
You got the castle without shedding blood.
-Praise be!
-You are providential as well.
You got spoils without
drawing your swords.
However Osman Bey,
you told us there were no treasure.
And we said it's alright.
No.
-We do not want it.
-What's that?
Are you disobeying my command?
-No, Osman Bey.
-It is most propitious to give to the ones that does not want it.
-Bora.
-Bey.
Distribute the Banerless' treasure.
As you command.
Konur.
And you maintain order of the castle
and come back to Yenisehir.
-As you command Bey.
-Come on.
Bannerless, quickly.
Osman Bey.
Do not call us "Bannerless" anymore.
We are fighting under the Banner of Kayi now.
Good.
Quickly.
Mehmet... So you were behind this, huh?
Isn't that him? From the Bannerless...
I swear... I won't let you have that...
...treasure you took with treachery.
My Shahzade.
We brought the Mongol clothes you wanted.
Good. Wear the clothes and paint your face.
We will raid their place.
How are you going to fight against
all those men with 6 people, Orhan?
Are you out of your mind?
Do not mind their number, Holofira.
Once, my ancestor Kursad...
...defeated everyone in a palace with his 40 valiants.
And now, with my 6 valiants...
..I will ruin them.
When I take the gold with my valiants,
I will prove myself...
...and gain my father's trust
Okay then. I will fight with you.
No.
You will not come.
You will stand back.
Alps.
Now listen to me carefully.
GERMIYANOGULLARI BORDER
Malhun Hatun.
Ulgen Hatun is also here.
Won't you feel a little upset
when you are stepping on...
...that carpet with your muddy feet, Ulgen?
I didn't know what to do.
I am trying to be silent and keep it in...
...Cerkutay does not know
what he is doing, but what about you?
Couldn't you inform me, Ulgen?
What does working in the marketplace mean?
Don't you know what's going to
happen when Osman Bey hears this?
How can't you resist Cerkutay?
I couldn't stop him no matter what I did.
Forgive me.
I thought you were my sister,
but what you did did not suit you, Ulgen Hatun.
You are now standing next to our enemy, not us.
I would never expect this from you.
Alps visited villages and tribes around Yenisehir.
They took all the carpets on the counters.
They will give them in the morning tomorrow.
Once Malhun Hatun's caravan is raided...
...and when she can't find goods to buy...
...let's see what she will
sell with an empty counter.
It is high time you approached Ulgen.
Be around her.
Mother... Saadet Hatun..
...wanted to buy all the carpets
in the villages and tribes around Yenisehir.
Hatuns sent news to ask what to do.
Saadet..
You want to play a game against me, huh?
When will they buy the carpets?
They said they would give those carpets
tomorrow morning to Alps to gain some time.
They are waiting for your order, mother.
I will play such a game against Saadet that...
...she won't even be able to understand.
We will send news to the Hatuns right away.
Now listen to me carefully.
Oguz Alp. Come on!
O Eternal!
Raid!
Come on!
Stay together!
Where are they?
O Eternal!
Protect the gold!
Protect the Shahzade!
O Eternal!
-Let's step back, Mehmed Bey.
-I won't leave the gold.
O Eternal!
Alps! Come on!
Who are you? Who are you?
We are stepping back! Come on!
Come on!
My Shahzade... My Shahzade...
Turahan!
Do you recognize the clothes of
the ones next to that caravan?
They wear our clothes,
but I don't know them, my Bey.
Osman Bey...
By the look of that caravan,
he is a wealthy trader.
e would know him if he was from here.
We'll see. We'll see now.
Peace be upon you.
With Allah's mercy and grace,
peace be upon you too,
-So you want to gain more good deeds, huh?
-Not at all, Osman Bey.
The Ummah is praying for you.
Our good deeds are nothing compared to yours.
You know us, you know what we look like.
But we don't know you. Tell me, who are you?
Where are you coming from?
Where are you going? Tell us.
Alps!
Bala, stand back. Stand back.
My Allah... My Allah, do not kill me today!
Alps! Alps! To the goods! Protect the goods!
Alps! The Bannerless! Come on!
We are even again, huh, Trickster Hatun?
I will defeat you next time, Scholar.
That's what you said earlier.
Look at you.. You are even again, huh?
Walk, Fatma. I couldn't follow Yakup Bey.
Good, but, I won't forget these...
We'll talk about it, know that brother.
Good, come on.
My son... Are you alright?
I am alright, mother.
But I lost track of Yakup Bey.
Malhun Hatun, my Shahzade.
We received news from Osman Bey.
Yakup Bey...
...conquered Lefke Castle and gave it to Osman Bey.
What is that man trying to do?
-My Shahzade...
He said you will keep following Yakup Bey.
This time we won't make a mistake.
Tell the Alps to go everywhere in the marketplace.
Everyone will be on alert.
Alaeddin. My son...
Then you will stay here tonight.
The carpet caravan is entrusted to you.
I think Saadet will raid the caravan...
...therefore, change your route.
Yes Malhun Ha tun.
Don't worry, Malhun mother.
I will send the Alps and take precaution.
Have you heard, brother?
Germiyan's son Yakup Bey...
...conquered Lefke Castle.
And he gave the castle to Osman Bey.
Yakup Bey really is an honorable man.
-Are you alright?
-Thank Allah, I am.
There's no need. There's no need at all.
Those crusaders are everywhere.
They cornered us, Osman Bey.
Thankfully we came across you
otherwise we would have been ruined.
-Thank you.
-No problem, no problem.
We wouldn't let infidels hurt you, of course.
Tell me now.
Who are you?
My Creator bestowed
upon us the profession of...
our Prophet (PBUH) and his companions.
As you can see, I'm a trader.
-They call me Ayhan agha.
-Ayhan agha, is that so?
-What do you have in your caravan?
-All sorts of things.
My Osman Bey, now,
I don't want to boast myself, but...
...I have such goods that
no one else has. I make trade with
traders from every nation.
My Osman Bey, this is our gift.
It is the most precious piece of my caravan.
It's not enough to pay for my life debt
but we would be glad if you accept.
Osman Bey.
It is our gift, we would be sad if you turn it down.
Thank you. Thank you.
Turahan, give it to me.
Take this in return.
No, take it.
We compensate everything we take.
Tell me, where are you headed at?
Osman Bey, I made my trade in Constantinople.
I'm going towards Karaman, but
I hope these infidels will not stop us again.
We were planning on going to the frontier marketplace.
Frontier marketplace?
-Do you know Yakup Bey?
-Yakup Bey? No.
I don't know him but I heard a lot
about the frontier marketplace.
It would be bad to not visit, but
I don't even want to go to a caravanserai anymore.
These dastards might attack again.
Ayhan agha, Ayhan agha we are very afraid!
Do not be afraid, do not be afraid!
Son of alps.
We brought them with us to teach them
trading but we cannot protect their lives.
That's not right.
Sons.
Move your caravan towards Yenisehir,
it is safer there.
Tomorrow come to my palace, we'll go to
the marketplace as well, you can join us.
May Allah bless you Osman Bey.
We'll surely come.
Sons, there's no need. Thank you.
May Allah bless you Osman Bey.
We will surely come.
-We'll be expecting.
-We will come.
-Have a safe journey.
Come on alps!
Come on!
I'll come, Osman. I will.
Bala. You'll go to Sogut, is that so?
You have made up your mind?
I have, Osman. Don't worry about me.
-As you see, I'm alright.
-I can see it my Bala.
Of course I do, but
I miss you my Bala.
I miss you.
With Allah's permission,
we'll be reunited soon.
I'll wait for it.
Turahan! Send Alps after Bala.
-Infidels might do something unexpected.
-Yes, my Bey.
Alps, come on
Come on, Osman. Have a safe journey
and good luck. Don't worry about the rest.
We'll ride our horses to our land, to Yenisehir.
Don't worry.
-May Allah protect you.
-Come on.
Yakup Bey.
You must have something on your mind,
but among all those beys who pledged loyalty to you,
-you gave the castle to Osman Bey.
-So?
-This might offend the Beys.
-Osman Bey
fought holy wars as their age and made
the Frontiers a nightmare for the infidels.
He even lost his brothers in this cause.
If someone gets offended
just because we showed favor
to such a Bey, let them get offended.
Osman thinks he is so smart.
He left his son in the marketplace as a spy.
Obviously, he is wondering
why did you give the castle, my Bey.
He's not convinced.
Let him seek as long as he wants, Hatun.
I was the one who gave it. I was.
If he doesn't obey now,
they will not be questioning my intentions,
they will be questioning his intentions.
They will say that Osman Bey...
...does not think about the holy case.
all he cares about is himself.
See? His followers are leaving him one by one.
He's getting lonely.
People, gather up!
Listen to me carefully.
Yakup Bey has conquered Lefke Castle.
And he gifted the castle to Osman Bey!
Let everyone know about this!
Come on!
Cerkutay is a different kind of man, Hatun.
We did very well by taking him by our side.
Let's set a table for tonight and invite him.
-We didn't get the chance to talk.
-Well thought.
Have it prepared.
-Welcome, father.
-Thank you.
I set a table for you.
I cooked half of the food myself, father.
What did you make for your father,
tell me about it.
I made fried meat.
I made kavut as a sweetener.
Praise be!
I cooked capitulum myself, father.
I love it. Thank you, thank you.
She is so talented, right?
She makes it very well,
thank you my daughter.
Come on, my beautiful daughter.
Bring the rest of them.
She thought you'd be upset
when you hear about Lefke.
So she started making foods.
She has a clean heart, thankfully.
Come on, have a seat.
Osman Bey, what's going to happen?
They even prevent us from gaining victories.
How it will end?
Yakup Bey is making plans in front of everyone,
but without anyone noticing it.
Of course, he is not the only one
who is making plans.
We will make a bigger plan.
Come on, my bey father.
The food is getting cold.
Bring it, dear.
Alright. Alright, let's start.
Alright. Let's get started.
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
Come on.
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
Let's start.
Praise be!
It's so delicious.
She's her mother's daughte
GERMIYANOGULLARI BORDER
So? Tell me, Cerkutay Bey.
What will you do to make the market flourish?
Kanyumaz will choose the alps having the gift of gab.
And we will send the goods of our market
to caravansary in small amounts.
But we won't take money in return.
We'll give away some of the goods.
We'll make people know our goods.
When they taste our goods,
they will flow into our market.
Then we will get much more in return.
I was right to count on your mind.
-Kanyumaz. You heard Cerkutay Bey.
-My Bey.
I heard, my Bey. As you order.
How could Osman Bey leave a man
like you behind for all those years?
You'll make the whole world know
about the market.
I hope so.
And those who didn't give you
the value you deserved...
...will knock their heads against
the wall with regret.
Cerkutay, eat some halvah.
She was so upset with the position we gave you.
She didn't think you deserved it.
The hatun who was under her command
for years is now almost equal to her.
-She must be surprised.
-You have a good heart, Ulgen Hatun.
You see what you want to see.
But your eyes must be open now.
You are representing me.
You should let nobody maltreat you.
Malhun Hatun in particular.
-Come on! Come on!
-Win! Win! Win!
Stop! Not against one, Ucar. Not again!
Take two men against you.
From the Bannerless.
Let the palace people see some strength!
-Choose!
-You.
You too.
Come on!
Even if that beast seems strong,
..he can't compete with you.
No. He's strong.
Are you afraid?
Ucar! Ucar!
I don't know that.
But you sound so enthusiastic, Gurbuz.
-Can you beat him?
-Just wait.
I know how to beat him.
You are so strong, huh, Bannerless?
The strength comes from mouth!
Is your mouth as strong as your muscles?
He can't even speak.
Alps, bring the molasses!
Let's see this man can compete with me...
..in the mouth race!
-Bring!
-Molasses!
Come on, bring it.
Come on, brother.
Let's start.
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
Drink! Drink! Drink!
Ucar will swallow it with bones!
Molasses can do nothing to him. Come on!
I'm burning!
Don't be! We have just started! Fill it.
Come on, Ucar. Don't disappoint us.
You swallowed a whole lamb!
Bamsi Bey and Turgut Bey
used to compete like this too.
Bring some water! He's burning!
We are well-trained, Bannerless.
Heat the square and burn it.
Make the Bannerless and
alps fight each other.
-Well done, brother.
-Good job, brother.
-You drank it well.
-Water.
Bring water! Water!
-Here it is.
-Water...
-Come on, drink it.
Enough. Don't drink too much.
You're not burning yet. Not yet.
Men, Kavruk can perform a good show.
-May he?
-Go ahead.
-Kavruk, show your skills.
-Kavruk! Kavruk!
Kavruk! Kavruk!
Know your place! You are guests here!
Who will teach us? You?
Yes!
Bannerless, break it up.
Back, stay back.
Know your place.
This is the palace of Bey, stop it.
Turahan, Aykut.
If Alps do the same again, its on you.
Gurdogan, Temirboga look at me.
The Bannerless will know their place.
They won't provoke Alps.
This is your last warning.
Now disperse.
What are you doing.
-My Shahzade, are you alright?
-I am alright Konur Bey.
Brother, call the healers quickly.
Sister, there is no need.
Where is father?
Come, brother.
-Can I come in?
-You may enter.
The caravan of Malhun has entered
the bazaar from another way Saadet Hatun.
They could not raid it.
Malhun.
Hold on, we arrived.
Can we come in Bey?
-Mehmet!
-Brother!
-My son! Mehmet!
-My Mehmet!
-Brother!
-Mehmet, my son!
-Mehmet!
-My Son!
-Mother!
-Brother!
-Call a healer!
-Alps!
-There are no healers.
-They went to Germiyan in the morning.
-Fitnat!
Go call a healer!
My valiant. Yakup Bey..
Mehmet, son!
-Yakup Bey.
-Mehmet!
Yakup Bey.
Careful Baysungur. Make no mistakes.
It is the order of Malhun Hatun.
Do not worry my Shahzade.
All rugs are carried.
-I will have the ones in cart on display.
-Alright.
-Make them keep watch for two weeks.
-As you command my Shahzade.
-Alaeddin.
-Gonca Hatun, what happened?
My brother is wounded.
We need your help Alaeddin Bey.
Quickly.
Bey, I have great news.
-I got the treasure.
-Praise be!
-And? What happened to you?
-However..
-I hit Mehmet, Bey.
-You did what?
What did you do my son?
Does he live? Did he see you?
I don't know how he is.
-I stepped on him.
-Orhan.
Bey, I checked..
He was alive.
And that savage can take it.
-Tell me what happened.
-Mehmet.
Made the bannerless wear crusader
outfit and pointed them to our way.
I hit them with their own trickery.
They think Mongols hit them.
Dumrul, come here.
-Bey.
-Go to the frontier bazaar.
-Check his situation.
-As you command, Bey.
Thanks to Holofira.
She never left beside me.
Thanks to your heart my girl.
Since the danger on the road is no more.
Then Holofira can return to her home.
-Mother, this is not the time to..
-Yes.
I want to return to my home as well.
Then as you wish, my girl.
You can depart in the morning.
Alps will accompany you to your home.
If you'll excuse me.
Father, if you allow me,
I want to accompany her as well.
You accompanied Holofira enough.
She will go with Alps, you'll come to bazaar with us.
-Mother.
-My son.
Don't make your mother say it twice.
As you command, Bey.
If you'll excuse me.
I understand that mother does not want Holofira..
-However, you were not this cruel Bey Father.
-Look at her.
Look what she's saying to her father.
Fatma, my dear daughte
Love is the greatest challenge for humans.
Let us wait first.
If your brother's love is just eagerness..
Or real, we will see.
Orhan Bey.
So it is time.
I am finally returning home.
Holofira. I do not want you to go.
Only you want me here, Orhan.
Your family think the same as me.
My departure will be good for all of us.
If you want to stay.
And if the problem is only
my mother, I will convince her.
I want to go, Orhan.
Maybe..
If we met on different terms..
-Whatever, take care of yourself.
-Holofira.
I...
always...
Do not make me suffer more.
My destiny brought you to me.
I will always wait for you, Lord's daughter.
Malhun... Malhun.
What if he really loves her?
What are we going to do then?
-You know he is stubborn.
-No. Marry him with someone as soon as possible.
We will find brides for both Orhan and Alaeddin.
-Fatma. Keep your eyes open.
-For my Alaeddin brother as well?
Look... What is wrong, Fatma?
-Do you know something?
-No, my Bey father.
I am surprised because both of my brothers
are going to get married at the same time.
Don't worry.
I'll look around.
Good then.
Hang on, my valiant.
Hang on, my son.
Hang on.
Yakup Bey! Stop.
We have to examine the wound first.
-Can you do it, Alaeddin Bey?
-Trust me. We don't have enough time.
He is losing too much blood.
We need a healer, Yakup Bey.
-Send news to everywhere!
-Mother, we don't have enough time!
Father! I trust Alaeddin Bey doubtlessly.
Please, move. We don't have time!
-Gonca!
-Mother, come on!
Come.
The wound is clean. There is no poison.
It doesn't seem deep. Baysungur, the bag!
Gonca Hatun. Prepare a cup.
He'll be alright, right?
Hang on, Mehmet.
Hang on.
Gonca Hatun.
Clean the wound.
Tell me something, Alaeddin. Will he be alright?
He lost too much blood.
He is weak right now, but his wound is not deadly.
-Kanyumaz!
-My Bey...
Find the one who shed my son's blood!
Hang on Mehmed Bey. Hang on.
O Healer! O Healer!
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
O Healer! O Healer!
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
Saadet Hatun.
Tell them to prepare sherbet for his blood loss.
I'll do it for my son. Come on, Fitnat.
When we also prepare a soup with broth,
my lion will get better.
My son will recover. Come on Fitnat.
Don't be afraid.
He'll be alright if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
-He'll be alright.
-Thank you.
Master Gera.
You came with your light.
Stand up, Vasilis.
-It's been a long time, Master Gera...
-Ah, time...
But you made use of that time very well.
You surrounded them from all sides.
You lit the first sparkle by killing Mesud.
Now we will start a big fire, Vasilis.
Thanks to your light, Master Gera.
Tell me about Osman's palace, Vasilis.
The people he trusts the most... Tell me, Vasilis.
He has Alps and Beys
who are even more loyal than apostles.
They are becoming a shield around Osman.
A shield..
We made a hole in that shield.
Cerkutay.
But we will destroy that shield.
Konur Bey..
...is leading Osman's army,
he is Osman's sword.
I gained his trust when I killed Remus.
-Who else?
-Bayindir Bey.
He is responsible of Osman's treasure and gold.
-Who else?
-Boran Bey.
He is Osman's closed book.
He can die for his Bey without hesitation.
He is loyal...
...he is in charge of the palace's order.
Especially its security.
Our target is Boran.
First... we will take him.
The palace will be defenseless. Osman...
...will stumble, he'll make a mistake.
Atmaca and the Bannerless
under his command...
...they are loyal to us.
We can defeat Boran anytime we want..
...and ruin Osman's palace.
The Bannerless, huh?
Yakup Bey is covering up his tracks.
Are you thinking about what our move
is going to be, my Osman?
Right.
But peace and union must be
present at the frontiers.
Therefore..
...if we need to obey Yakup Bey...
-Obey?
That's why Yakup Bey is playing
all those games.
You are thinking about something else.
You make your preparations.
Don't worry.
GERMIYANOGULLARI BORDER
I owe you a life, Scholar.
-My Alps...
-Brother?
Brother?
-My Alps...
-He is waking up.
-Thank to Allah.
Good... Good.
You are too tired.
It will strengthen you as well.
Thank you.
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
Father... My brother is waking up!
Mehmed!
-Father...
-Thank to Allah, my son.
My strong son... My lion son..
-Mother...
-He must drink his sherbet.
My Mehmed..
I boiled healing herbs and
put it in this bottle.
This will take his pain away InshaAllah.
Thank you Alaeddin Bey.
My Mehmed, I am here.
I will not forget this favor, Alaeddin Bey.
Now, Germiyan owes you a life.
Kanyumaz!
Take it.
No thank you, Yakup Bey.
I did my duty.
There is no need for a gift.
Thank you.
You are both brave..
...and pure-hearted, huh?
It is apparent that you are Sheikh Edebali's grandson.
Thank you.
It's alright, Yakup Bey, it's alright.
With Allah's mercy and grace,
peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
-Welcome, Ayhan Bey.
-Thank you.
Make way! Osman Bey!
Welcome. Is your caravan safe?
-How are the children, are they well.
-May Allah bless you.
Thankfully, they are alright, we are so relieved.
Good, good. So, we heard about you.
You have visited Yenisehir downtown.
I have, Osman Bey. Praise be.
It's has nothing less than
the markets in Konya.
If you'll excuse me, I'd like to trade
with a few shopkeepers.
Is that so? Then let me introduce
you to Bayindir Bey.
He is responsible for the order
of Yenisehir's downtown.
He is very good at it. Thank you.
Thank you.
My Bey orders and I do my duty.
Ayhan Agha will come to the
Frontier marketplace with us.
You will introduce him to
the shopkeepers there.
Sure, my Bey.
My Bey.
My Bey, ten thousand gold has been loaded to the cars.
The rest has been delivered to the treasury.
With Allah's permission, the Germiyan marketplace
will witness a glory it has never seen before.
Praise be! Praise be!
Thank you.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
I don't want a single breach of security in the palace.
You are responsible for the security.
-I'll do my best, my Bey.
-I don't want any mistake.
Come on. We'll go to the Frontier's marketplace.
Osman Bey.
Give us orders too. We don't want to be out of practice.
Let us fight, let us raid.
You want war, is that so?
What do you have on your mind? To where?
-Whatever you wish, Osman Bey.
-No.
Go to the outpost.
Konur, Turahan.
-You will go to the outpost with them.
-Yes, my Bey.
Bala, do you want something?
Now..
...I only have my Alaeddin with me.
But it seems...
...he will still have a mother.
-Shush, Bala.
Don't say that. Don't.
Protect him.
I trust him to you, Malh
I trust him to you.
-Bala.
-Don't get closer.
Promise me.
I promise you, Bala.
I promise you.
You kept that promise very well.
You protected my trust, Malhun.
-Bala.
Thank my Creator that you are alright.
I'm alright.
Your test was so harsh Bala.
We have passed those tests all together, Malhun.
Come on, come.
How are you? How are the children?
Don't ask about it Bala.
They grow and their problems grow as well.
You must have heard Holofira is back.
It seems Orhan still loves Holofira.
-So she will be the bride?
-May Allah forbid.
She can't be the bride. Holofira will go
back to her home before it gets any longer.
They must have set out already.
But you say he loves her.
How are we going to stop Orhan?
I have something
on my mind, but...
I think we should find someone for Orhan and Alaeddin.
So you only want daughter of Beys.
You talked about the test just now,
you know why I accepted such a big test, Bala.
I saw a dream with Osman Bey.
Of course, nothing we went through was easy, but
we both suffered this test for
the dream we saw in Osman Bey.
And we're still enduring it.
Now we need daughters-in-law
who will keep this dream just like we do.
You are right. Let's take a look around, then.
I'll inform the Hatuns.
I should get going, Bala. Yakup Bey invited me
to the marketplace, I shouldn't be late.
About the marketplace,
what did Osman Bey decide on?
I guess he will be by Yakup Bey's side.
-What do you think?
-I don't know Bala.
It seems the fact that Yakup Bey is fighting
holy wars convinced Osman Bey.
He fights holy wars but at the same time
he makes all sorts of plans behind us.
I know. I know but I guess Osman Bey
has something on his mind.
I'm waiting for your orders, sir.
Get ready, Atmaca.
We'll take the gold back from Osman.
Gather the bannerless ones who are loyal to us.
I know, master Vasilis.
We will be even faster than the wind.
May it be easy.
In love's market, lives in display,
mine I offer, but none to convey.
They proclaim the death of lover,
yet it is the nafs that die...
lovers do not die.
They think they are dead,
yet they wander, even bolder
they let the nafs win the fight
the lover's warmth grows colder.
Welcome, Dervish.
So the reputation of our marketplace
even reached to the guild.
The reputation of your marketplace.
Yes, it did.
Where are you coming from?
What do you want to buy, let me help you.
I come from Hayy
But I'm not here to buy, I'm here to sell.
-To sell?
Which counter did we give? What do you sell?
I'm here to sell lives, but
lives are sold in the marketplace of love.
It seems this is just the marketplace of wrath and ambition.
I can't set a counter here for life.
What wrath, what ambition did you see here,
Dervish Effendi.
What else can be found in the place of living ones?
You are looking for dead men in the marketplace.
The dead is in the tomb.
In human, there are two beings.
One is the skin and the other one is the life.
The skin belongs to this world and
the life belongs both of the worlds.
Sultan of the worlds Rasulullah (PBUH)
says that "Before you die, you shall die."
Skin shall be alive, you should kill your nafs.
The one that dies before he dies
knows that he is incapable.
This world is a guestroom and this skin is a trust.
If human does not die before he dies,
he wanders around on earth,
he says "I can break the ground"
"I can climb up to that mountain."
He gets angry, gets ambitious.
His pride becomes his master.
The marketplace of those who killed
their nafs is the marketplace of love,
and the marketplace of those
who are the slaves of their nafs
is the marketplace of wrath. So,
in the tombs, there are those whose skins are dead
but we are looking for those who killed their nafs.
But it seems
no one here wants to die before he dies.
See you.
Don't let me lose sight of who I am,
Greed clouds my vision,
The earth's cycle, in constant flow,
Good and bad arrive, then they go.
In the hereafter, one hopes and prays
But a dervish Yunus says,
"The Eternal is here, and here He lays"
Before you die,
..you shall die.
My Bey, welcome.
-Thank you.
-This is our place.
-Welcome, my Bey.
Thank you, son. Thank you.
This is it, huh?
O people! Hear ye! Hear ye!
Here is Osman Bey's gift! Those having a son
shall not be upset for not being able to have a wedding!
Those having a daughter shall not be upset
for not being able to prepare dowry!
Everybody in debt, gather up!
-May Allah be pleased with Osman Bey.
-Thank you.
He's here! Osman Bey is here!
Oh, my Cerkutay.
Look. Look at me.
-Have you grown tall?
Yes, my Bey. Can I be an alp now?
Be patient.
You need some more time to be an alp.
Look at me. Praise be.
You will grow fast.
I miss you so much, my Bey.
Me too, boy.
Me too. Come on.
-Let me show you around the market, Osman Bey.
-Alright.
Good. Good, good. Order!
Order matters! I don't want to see
these sacks here again. Come on!
Cerkutay, Osman Bey is here.
Don't, Ulgen. Don't let him maltreat you.
Come on. Let's go say welcome to Osman Bey.
What do you think about the market?
Well... The market
can grow easily.
But what matters is its location.
It's on the road linking the west with the east.
It's near Yalakova Port.
Yakup Bey chose a right spot.
You say it will make those who
sell goods here grow bigger too, huh?
Yes, but what matters is who it will make grow with it.
Fine. Let's see the stands.
Peace be upon you! Good day!
You'll enter Osman's palace as servants.
We'll take all his gold.
-We will!
-And vengeance..
We will hit Boran who Osman trusts most...
...in his palace which he feels safest.
Osman will lose another part of his.
-He will lose his sleep.
-Sir.
How will we get rid of Osman's men?
They will want to check the chests.
Putting those fools to sleep is my job, Atmaca.
You finish your preparations.
Today, we are going to destroy
Osman's palace.
-Have a good one!
-May Allah be please with you, my Bey.
-May Allah be pleased with you too.
-Thanks, my Bey.
Thank you too.
Thank you! Thank you!
Welcome, Osman... Bey.
Thank you, Cerkutay......... Bey.
This duty looks good on you.
You deserve this.
Yakup Bey gave me this title, thankfully.
-Cerkutay, come here. Don't disturb Osman Bey.
-No.
-I missed Osman Bey. I'll stay with him.
-Oh, boy...
-Cerkutay.
-Just wait.
Just wait.
Boy, you should go now.
-I will come again, my Bey. Don't worry.
-Of course. Whenever you want.
Ayhan Agha.
You say this market will make
the sellers grow bigger, huh?
Yes, Osman Bey.
I'm a tradesman of this time.
When I look, I can see the earning
and loss from a distance.
I want this market to make you grow.
I owe you a life.
Well... What should we do then?
It's your decision. But if I were you,
I would buy at least the half of this market.
Hey, you are convincing!
You'll almost make me buy the whole market.
Now tell me.
Is this for your interest or my interest?
For the interest of both of us, Osman Bey.
Good. Good.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, thank you.
Thank you! Thank you!
-You should rest more, Mehmed.
-I'm good, mother.
If jackals see the wolf wounded,
they become willing to fight.
Praise be to you.
Even if you bleed, you shouldn't fall down.
Thank you father.
Did you finish?
Almost, my Bey.
After counting this chest.
Make no mistakes. Careful brother,
or Bayindir Bey won't stop talking.
May Allah prevent it Bey.
-Alright, let me know when it is finished.
-Thank you Bey.
Come on.
Quickly, take everything away.
Come on don't occupy the courtyard.
When will you take these from here,
horses will go out.
Don't worry, I will take care of it.
Quickly, quickly.
Thank you, Bey.
May Allah bless our Bey.
Osman Bey.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too, Yakup Bey.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
We are welcomed.
Then, where does this money come from?
You are giving away your gold.
Was it inheritance or did you do some digging?
Why do you ask? Are you keeping our gold counted?
-We claimed a big debt, that is it.
-Okay.
Your wealth can only make me happy, Osman Bey.
That is what I thought as well.
Look here, I want to buy all of these stalls here.
I thought you would be happy if I had more stalls here.
-Osman Bey.
-Everyone..
Has equal rights, Osman Bey.
-We do not want a single hand in our bazaar.
-The stalls Osman Bey pointed..
Are equal of yours, Saadet Hatun.
To make it not single hand, it must be made equal.
Praise be.
What are you going to do with these stalls?
Do you have goods to sell in that inheritance?
Come, come here. Here is Ayhan Agha.
We made a deal with him.
He has brought the biggest caravan this land has ever seen.
In these stalls, we will sell his goods.
-Welcome to our bazaar, Ayhan Agha.
-I am welcomed, Yakup Bey.
Where do you come from?
I've never seen you before.
There is not much time to visit home, Yakup Bey.
From Damascus to Samarkand..
And to Indian land to the land of Greek, I set my caravan.
I will make your bazaar, and our Osman Bey,
very wealthy.
-If Allah permits.
If Alalh permits.
-Bayindir Bey.
-Bey.
Go to those stalls,
speak with their owners.
Pay a little more than
what they put to their goods..
-And buy them all.
-As you command.
Cerkutay Bey, take care of Bayindir Bey,
so the business is done right.
As you command, Yakup Bey.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
-Ready the arbour.
-As you command, Bey.
You are invited, Osman Bey.
Let us go then.
Be quick, we can not wait here.
Tell me, Ayhan Agha.
What business do you do?
Whatever that land needs, Yakup Bey.
I load a big caravan.
While the head of the caravan leaves city..
The back of it must not have left it. However..
A lot of Alps and soldiers
are needed for protection.
Issues like these are not a problem
in my land, do not worry.
I will provide protection.
Very well.
Yakup Bey. Sorry to say this.
However, we will provide
protection for this caravan.
We already made a deal.
Then why would we buy these stalls?
Of course. Osman Bey will protect our caravan.
-Of course they will protect it well.
-Of course we will.
We always protect those with us, Mehmet Bey.
Goods have safely arrived Saadet Hatun.
-What is it Saadet Hatun?
You didn't leave any rugs on frontiers
what are you going to do with them?
For business.
You resented much for these rugs.
Take no offence.
No, just out of curiosity.
Open one and let's see how are they.
Come on.
Fitnat! Why are they like this!
-Alps!
-The rugs were wrapped.
We never thought of looking inside.
We've just been told to pick them up.
Open the rest.
Hatuns will deliver the rugs wrapped
to the alps that will come for pick up.
They will give the unsold and
left-behind rugs to Saadet Hatun.
You are very cunning, mother.
She can not use let alone sell those rugs.
We will make those pay,
who insult the hard work of Kayi Tribe.
All of them are like this.
Well, Saadet Hatun..
It seems you collected all the
flawed rugs in the frontiers.
Luckily, the news ones showed up
thanks to you.
Well...
These are no good for trading.
Why did you buy them?
Didn't you check at all?
Hatuns, unroll our rugs!
Let people see the fine quality.
Fools.
My Bey, as you ordered,
we bought all the stands.
Thank you, thank you.
Everything has been handled properly,
Yakup Bey.
Yet..
Since the tribe people are privileged,
...Ayhan Agha's goods
coming from the other lands....
..will be taxed double.
No problem.
Whatever the owner of the market says,
...we will comply with it.
That's good.
Those who want no problems will obey...
...what the owner says. Both the peace...
...and unity can only be provided like this.
Ayhan Agha said well.
If the decision is made truthfully..
..then no one will stand against it, Yakup Bey.
The decision is right.
The one who obeys the right decision...
...always gets his reward.
Ayhan Agha.
You proved your commercial morality...
..by not objecting.
You will pay the same amount of tax
like everyone else.
We always reward our companions.
Yakup Bey...
Now you are making a decision
because Ayhan Agha...
...accepted your dominance.
But this land is not only the
marketplace of frontiers...
It is not a land of traders who sell their...
..votes for rewards.
-See the difference.
-Osman Bey.
Allah is the Greatest!
-O Allah.
-Allah is..
Great Allah..
Great Allah.,
-...the Greatest!
Anyway.
Let's not go on and on
about the issue.
Cerkutay Bey...
Help Ayhan Agha settle in his tent.
And we will perform salaat with
Osman Bey and then have dinner.
Let's talk about what..
...dominance and sultanate are.
Sure.
How could you do this?
You bought all the faded...
..old and damaged carpets!
Didn't you look at them for once, Fitnat?
Since we said "buy all the carpets"
to our Alps...
...they did not check.
They bought all of them.
-Can I come in, Saadet Hatun?
-Come in.
What is wrong, Saadet Hatun?
You seem angry.
Did you lose your money?
How can these carpets make us lose money?
Who do you think Germiyans are?
This is the gold for the damaged
carpets you bought. It is all here.
What are you trying to do?
We do not sell flawed goods, Saadet Hatun.
And I know why you
wanted to buy those carpets.
What does that mean?
Is it a mistake to trade now?
Trade?
Anyway. Now you learnt...
You cannot sell a single thing
without informing me at the frontiers.
Fitnat! Take this gold and
give it to our people!
This can only be my charity to the poor!
I will make you pay for this Malhun.
I will.
Come on! This way!
GERMIYANOGULLARI BORDER
I organized this dinner and let only
two families attend on purpose.
I wanted our dinner to be genuine.
I wanted our friendship to be stronger.
I wanted the words which couldn't
be said in front of other people...
..to be said around this table.
Why would the ones who are always
honest and blunt in a crowd...
...need to be alone to say their words?
Fair enough.
May what you eat and drink be yours.
Now I will talk about our actual issue.
Sure we will. Let's talk about conquests.
We took Lefke for a reason.
Not conquests, Osman Bey...
We will talk about conquests after you pledge allegiance.
I proved that my only intention
was conquering lands...
...with the conquest of Lefke.
I also proved that my intention was being a union...
...by giving Lefke to you. Now you..
...can prove that fighting for Islam,
conquests and union are your goals.
We all know each other.
-Announce your obedience, Osman Bey.
-Yakup Bey.
Yakup Bey.
Taking the castle before methat
I was already acting on..
Doesn't prove anything.
None of these things you said,
are a reason to obey.
They are in the treasure room.
Get ready, quickly.
Who are you?
Atmaca, someone's coming.
Quickly.
Quickly, faster.
Orhan Bey. There you are.
Alps! Some got in!
You go and help them get the treasure.
Your mask won't save you, devil.
Come here! Come!
-Bey!
-The treasure.
-Treasure.
Bey! Orhan Bey!
Bey! Hold on Bey!
Atmaca, Vasilis is coming.
Alps are coming.
Get out from the barn quickly.
Follow me.
Alps!
I killed their leader.
I couldn't catch their leader,
they ran away.
They went towards the kitchen.
You go after them.
There is no unity like this.
You create a duality.
This is no time to create duality.
Why am I the one causing conflict?
Tell me.
Did I tell you do not be the Sultan
Your banner is different.
And mine is different.
Having two heads is the same as
having no head at all.
It's not right, Osman Bey. It is not!
What are you worried about?
Tell me Yakup Bey.
are you afraid that all of the
Beys will gather behind me?
Stop there. Stop it.
The pledge you are talking about is not
for the sake of holy case.
It is for the sake of suppressing your rival.
-Osman Bey!
-Stop.
Are you equal to me
that you can be my rival?
I see you as my brother,
having the same blood as you.
It might result in a disaster
if you do not pledge loyalty to me.
Evil ones may cause conflict. No.
I will not let you do that to our country.
Now I will ask one last time.
Are you with me or are you against me?
Yakup Bey.
The one who stays in the
shadow has no shadow.
dreamed about that plane tree that
will be the shadow of many oppressed ones.
And now you want me to forget about my dream.
Inform the healers!
No one will leave the palace...
-...until we find those men!
-I bear witness that none worthy of worship except Allah
and I bear witness that Muhammad (PBUH)
is His servant and Messenger.
My Bey! Hang on my Bey!
But I see that you are after the same dream.
You didn't leave us in a tight spot.
You gave us the castle you took by fighting.
Even more,
you protected my brave boy.
I know that your intentions are well.
If we do not stray away from
the path of Allah's words...
I'll be behind you from now on.
Then pledge your loyalty Osman Bey.
From now on,
Kayis will obey Germiyanoglus.
Since you pledged loyalty and we have united,
let all the conflicts end. Come on.
Come on, come here. Come on.
Come on.
We will be behind
you from now on.
It will be a new beginning for all of us.